I took it out a little, so let's take a look inside.
ちょっと中を出しちゃったから、中を見てみようか、
Try putting it in.
入れてみてよ
Is it possible?
いけそう?
Oh, pull out, pull out.
お、引き出る引き出る
Okay, let me make it stick out a little too much.
ちょっとじゃあ、はみ出をしすぎてもらいます
Oh la la la la la, look.
あらららららら、見て
Stillness.
静止が
I can't see it.
見えなー
I can change this without washing it.
これ洗わずに変えるんだよ
yeah?
ん?
Change it without washing it.
洗わずに変えるんだよ
no.
いや
picture?
え?
I'll wash it.
洗うよ
Judging by the contract.
契約で判断する
what?
何?
picture?
え?
This hiragana is amazing.
これ、ひらがすごいだろ
You don't have to cut it out, so try pulling it out and putting it in a little bit.
抜き切んなくていいから、ちょっと抜いたり入れたりしてみよう
mosquito.
か
Yeah, yeah, pull it out.
そうそう そう、抜いて
Let's pull it out a little more.
もうちょっと抜こう
Yes, pull it out.
はい、抜いて
Yes, put it in.
はい、入れて
It's so fluttering.
すっごいひらひらだね
My hair is so fluttery.
髪がすごいひらひらだ
It hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い
picture?
え?
Yeah.
うん
So, do you understand?
じゃあ、分かる?
There's a fluttering.
ひらひらがあるんだよ
Where?
どこに?
I don't know.
分からない
Of course, I was in and out and in and out.
当然、入ったり出したり入ったりしてて
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's go to sleep.
じゃあ、寝ていきましょう
I don't like it.
嫌
Then, splash some water on your face.
じゃあ、顔水かけてね
I don't like it.
嫌よー
Yes.
はーい